当我闭上双眼，
When I close my eyes,
我听见。
I hear things.
马车经过时，它的轮子
The sound of a carriage passing
跟鹅卵石路撞出的声音。
as its wheels wobble against the cobblestone paths.
我淡出于包裹著我的人群的嘈杂声。
I fade softly against the murmurs of the crowds that encompass me.
风铃明明被狂风吹著，
Wooden chimes are faintly heard
却没人听的到它的声音。
against the howling wind.
我听不清。
Unknown to me.
当我闭上双眼，
When I close my eyes,
我看见。
I see things.
我看见她，笑著回头看我，
I see her smiling back at me,
就像我记忆中的那样，
just like I remembered her doing,
那是多么遥远，当时事情还没这么复杂。
long ago when things were simpler.
我看见我，在镜子里面，
I see myself in the mirror.
晚上作梦时，我知道镜子里的是我，
In my dreams, I know it's me,
白天醒著时，我却是开始怀疑自己。
but in the daylight, I can never be sure.
艳丽的青与赤在天上飞舞，但老实说，再怎么美丽，
Brilliant blues and pinks cascade across a sky that, to be honest,
我都从没抬头看过。
I never look up at.
没什么好特别的。
This is nothing profound.
当我闭上双眼，
When I close my eyes,
我梦见。
I dream of things.
但他们只不过
But they're only familiar
仅只于
to the point
我心中
of a feeling
的感受。
that I know it.
我闭上双眼，
I close my eyes
在花凋叶落前我都不要醒来。
and dream until every petal falls.
当我闭上双眼，
When I close my eyes,
我试著忘记张眼时的感觉。
I try to forget what it's like to keep them open.
当我闭上双眼，
When I close my eyes,
我试著忘记他们的责骂。
I try to forget the blame.
当我闭上双眼，
When I close my eyes,
我试著记好我的名字。
I try to remember my name.